telltalegames.com 2019-09-04

# Privacy Policy – Telltale Games

**Welcome!**

LCG Entertainment, Inc. the owner of Telltale brands. LCG/Telltale values its fans and customers, and we are glad to have you visit us. We are committed not only to making great games, but also to respecting the privacy rights of everyone who visits and uses our website or our online services. This Privacy Policy provides a guide as to how we serve as a data controller and outlines how we collect, store and use the information that you provide to us online (including personal information, as defined below, and information provided during online game play) and explains how we may share information. LCG/Telltale acts as the data controller regarding the personal information we collect from you. This Privacy Policy will also let you know how you can change the way we may collect personal information from you. We also discuss notices of changes that may be made to this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy applies to our online mobile products and services (collectively, the “Services”) as well as any website owned or controlled by LCG/Telltale, and references to a “Site” are applicable to all such websites including www.Telltale.com and www.Telltalegames.com . This Privacy Policy does not apply towards any information that we may collect from you offline. If LCG/Telltale changes this Agreement, your continued use or access of the Site constitutes acceptance of such change. BY USING ANY OF OUR SITES OR OUR ONLINE MOBILE PRODUCTS AND SERVICES, YOU AGREE TO ALL OF THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, INCLUDING ANY CHANGES TO IT. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE, PLEASE DO NOT USE OUR SITES OR SERVICES.

**What information do we collect and how is it used?**

The type of information that LCG/Telltale collects will vary depending on the activity collected and may include what is known as “personally identifiable information” or “personal information” including your first and last name, e-mail address, account information for certain third party sites or networks such as Facebook or Twitter, phone numbers (including cell phone numbers), home address, and zip code. Personally identifiable information can be accessed in order to directly contact you. This information is collected so that visitors can participate in activities such as receiving our newsletters or participating in contests, surveys or sweepstakes (your participation in contests, surveys or sweepstakes may require you to provide additional personally identifiable information such as a phone number, age or gender). Third parties may contact you to participate in surveys on our behalf, and third parties may also contact you to participate in Promotions as we discuss more fully below. We also collect additional types of personally identifiable information (e.g., credit card and billing and shipping information, including physical addresses and phone numbers) when someone purchases products and offerings at our Sites or through use of our Services. Such purchases are governed by our Terms of Service, http://www.Telltalegames.com/termsofservice , the terms and conditions of which are incorporated herein by reference. We may share your personal information with third parties solely in order to have them assist with fulfillment of product sales, including shipping and credit card processing, and companies that assist us with e-mailings, but such third parties agree to maintain the security of your personal information in a manner consistent with this Privacy Policy.

We may also share personal information with third parties to prevent abuse of our Site or Services and also to comply with any laws, notices or orders from a governmental agency or entity or to prevent harm to a user of our Site or Services.

Some of our Sites and Services use Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses “cookies,” which are text files placed on your computer, to help us analyze and track how visitors use the Site and our Services. The information generated by the cookie about your use of our Services will be transmitted to and stored on Google servers and may be accessed by us. Google uses this information to help us evaluate how our websites are used. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google’s behalf. Third party sites and services you access through our Services may also employ cookies.

Cookies also allow us to see what you may have purchased, either from our Site or through using one of our Services including game play. We collect information on our online games you have played, and we also track your play within an online game (including online games you may have purchased from a third party website) and, if such are available, purchases that you may make within an online game. We may send you notifications based on information we learn from cookies, including notifications related to purchasing additional games or products from us.  
LCG/Telltale also collects IP addresses (an IP address is the string of numbers that identifies each sender or receiver of information that is sent across the Internet), for the purposes of system administration, to report aggregate information internally and to some of our business partners and advertisers and to audit the use of our Sites or Services. When visitors request pages on one of our Sites, our servers log the visitors’ IP addresses. We collect log files that record activity on our Sites and gather statistics about visitor’s time and activity on the Sites. The statistics are generated anonymously, and they help us in connection with marketing and demographic studies as we enhance our Sites. LCG/Telltale does not normally link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable, which means that a user’s session will be logged, but the user remains anonymous to us. LCG/Telltale can and will use IP addresses to identify a user when we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with our Terms of Service, this Privacy Policy or to protect our services, Sites or a person or entity. Third parties providing services or technology on our behalf may also collect certain information such as IP addresses of our users; however, such information is provided on an aggregated basis and is not tracked to an individual user.

We may also use cookies to track postings to online discussions about our Services that are controlled by us. While you can disable cookies, some areas of our Site or our Services may not function with all available features if you do so.

You can manage Cookie settings by navigating to and opening the “Help” menu on the browser menu bar. Generally, browsers will let you how you can disable or delete Cookies or set your browser to alert you when Cookies are being sent to your computer. If you do not allow all Cookies, you may not be able to use various features of our Sites or Services.

Your use of the Sites or our Services means that we will assume that you consent to receive cookies from us unless you have changed your cookie choices as discussed above.  
If we are going to use your personal information in a manner that is materially different from that stated at the time of collection, we will post a notice prominently on our Sites and may also make a modification to this Privacy Policy. You will have a choice as to whether or not we use your information in this different manner. In some cases where we post the notice we may also email users, who have opted to receive communications from us, notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices.

We may share some aggregate data that we learn about users (which is data that does not contain personal information) with third parties.

**Targeted Advertising**

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve you targeted ads on our behalf, and we may share personally identifiable information that we collect about you with those third party companies, and they may also collect personally identifiable information about you as described in this Privacy Policy. These companies provide ads that are relevant to you based on data that is collected or content on our Site that you have been viewing. These companies may employ cookies both to measure advertising effectiveness and also to collect data related to your activity on our Sites. That data may include your browsing activity, for example what web pages you may have visited on our Site; device and browser information, which is technical information about the device or browser you use to access or site; data about the ads that have been served (or an attempt made to serve) to you, including things like how many times an ad has been served to you, what page the ad appeared on and whether you clicked on or otherwise interacted with the ad; and, your IP address. We have no access to or control over these cookies once we have given permission for third parties set cookies for advertising.

You can opt-out of receiving targeted ads served by third party advertising companies on our behalf by visiting any of the following websites: www.aboutads.info or www.networkadvertising.org/choices/ . Those in Europe may visit the European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance opt-out site located at www.youronlinechoices.eu. Additional information about targeted ads is available from the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”), whose website is located at: www.networkadvertising.org. You may also opt-out of targeted ads delivered by NAI member ad networks by visiting the NAI website. Please note that if you opt-out from receiving targeted ads we may still collect some data about your online activity for operational purposes (such as fraud prevention) but it will not be used for the purposes of serving targeted ads. Also, if you use multiple browsers or devices, you may need to use one of the applicable opt-out websites to execute an opt-out for each browser or device.  
Data Transfer to the United States

LCG/Telltale operates its Sites within the United States. The personal information that you may provide or that we otherwise collect may be stored on (or transferred to) servers located in the United States or other countries where we may engage in business. Information collected within the European Economic Area may be transferred to the United States, and you agree to any such international transfers of your personal information in accordance with applicable law.  
Electronic Newsletter and Subscription to other Updates about LCG/Telltale  
LCG/Telltale offers users the opportunity to sign up to receive the LCG/Telltale monthly newsletter as well as news, web, game and press updates related to LCG/Telltale (collectively, “Updates”). LCG/Telltale does not guarantee or promise the frequency in which Updates may be sent and reserves the right to discontinue sending Updates at any time. To sign up for Updates, you must be eligible to register with LCG/Telltale and provide your e-mail address, first name, create a password and, at your option, a screen name.

Information collected for LCG/Telltale Updates may be transferred, disclosed, or shared with third parties who may be engaged by us specifically to handle the preparation and delivery of the Updates and perform other related technical and processing functions. These third parties may not use it for other purposes and have agreed to maintain the confidentiality of such information.  
Sign-up for Updates is always optional and done with your consent, and users who no longer wish to receive our updates and communications may opt-out of receiving these communications by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link in the email or email us at optout@Telltalegames.com , or you may contact us by post at LCG/Telltale, Inc., Attn: LCG Entertainment, Inc. c/o Law Office of Dan Lee Rogers P.O. Box 1233 Oakhurst, CA 93644 to opt-out.

**Forums**

At your own discretion, and once you meet certain eligibility requirements, you may choose to post or upload additional facts and material about yourself and your profile, including a biography, birth date (with the year being optional) a profile picture, your location, your interests or your occupation. Such postings may be made on the “Forums” section of our Site, which are governed by the Terms of Service and this Privacy Policy. Such additional facts and material can be entered (or changed) on the “Edit My Profile” section of the Forums. LCG/Telltale’s Forums are used for exchanging information and social networking. Please note that information, additional facts or any other materials that you post anywhere on our Sites, including any information or materials that you choose to make public on the Forums, will be available for any user to read, and are therefore no longer private. A third party may disclose any information or materials you choose to post. Also, information and material that you post could be used by someone to send you unsolicited messages. Once posted, you cannot change or remove any public postings made in our Forums or other message areas (although LCG/Telltale reserves the right to remove any such public postings in its sole discretion), and we are not responsible for the personally identifiable information or material you choose to submit. We reserve the right to terminate the accounts of visitors who use these services in a manner inconsistent with our Terms of Service.  
Personal Information from Third Parties/Social Networking Sites  
Provided that you have first given permission to the applicable third party, LCG/Telltale may receive information from third party social networking sites, including Facebook and Twitter, related to your accounts on those services. Information that we collect from those third parties from whom you have given permission may be used by LCG/Telltale solely in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy. Some users who access our Services through a social networking account such as Facebook or through our Site may receive access to special content not available to other users.

We may also collect personal information about you from online distributors of our games such as Steam, Microsoft Xbox LIVE and the Sony Entertainment Network where you play our games on their respective distribution networks. The information we may receive is personal information related to your account on these respective distribution networks but does not include financial information such as credit card information. We may store and use the information we receive about you from online distributors of our games and social networks in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy.

**Policy Against Unsolicited Submissions**

As further described in our Terms of Service, please note that LCG/Telltale has a policy against accepting unsolicited material, so we ask that you do not submit any unsolicited or unique creative ideas, drawings or other materials to LCG/Telltale directly or otherwise in connection with any posts you make to the Forums or in connection with additional facts or material you may provide in any posting on any of our Sites.

**Special Promotions, Online Contests and Sweepstakes**

LCG/Telltale and its advertisers and/or other business partners may have special online promotions, contests or sweepstakes (collectively, “Promotions”) which feature products or services related to LCG/Telltale’s business activities. For most Promotions, you must be 13 years or older to participate (unless otherwise specified by the promotions’ rules and regulations). Also, if you are under 18 years of age or otherwise considered a minor, and if you are eligible to participate in a Promotion (including, eligibility for registration with LCG/Telltale), you will need your parent’s or guardian’s written consent to collect your prize or receive any benefit to which you may be entitled. If you have won a prize, we may also collect your physical address and phone number. For other Promotions, we may request your name and home address in order to send you products or information by regular mail. The specific rules and regulations governing the particular Promotions will vary and your participation constitutes your agreement to abide by those rules and regulations.

**Third Party Links**

To provide relevant information not found on our Sites, LCG/Telltale may provide links from our Sites to third party websites. We encourage our users to read third party websites’ privacy policies before submitting personal information.  
Correspondence With LCG/Telltale  
If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or postings on our Sites or Services, we may collect such information into a file which is only accessed by authorized personnel. We may also collect other users’ comments about you in our complaints department.  
Your use of Other Users’ Information  
You may not use other users’ information for commercial purposes, to spam, to harass, or to make unlawful threats. LCG/Telltale reserves the right to terminate those who misuse other users’ information or who otherwise violate the LCG/Telltale Terms of Service.

**Control of Your Password**

You may not disclose your password to any third parties or share it with any third parties. If, despite the foregoing, you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personally identifiable information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately change your password.

**Reviewing, Changing or Deleting Your Personally Identifiable Information**

Please promptly update your information if it changes by logging in to your account and following the screen prompts. We strongly urge you to periodically change your password to help reduce the risk of unauthorized access to your account information. We will retain in our files information, including personal information, you have requested to remove in some circumstances to comply with our legal obligations such as to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, comply with contest rules and law, comply with industry rules and regulations, enhance security, reduce fraud, comply with applicable law and to enforce our Terms of Service.

Once you register, you can request that any inaccuracies about your personal information be corrected. You can also ask about whether and why we have your personal information; how we obtained it; what we have done with it; to whom we communicated your personal information; where it has been stored, processed or transferred; how long we will retain it; and, the safeguards that are in place to protect your personal information when it is transferred to third parties. You can also ask us not to collect or use your personal information for certain purposes. Depending on which laws apply to your personal information, we may only be able to do some of these things for you. If you request one of these things and we refuse to do it, we will explain your legal rights, the reason for our refusal and any recourse you may have. We will respond to your request without undue delay within 30 days. LCG/Telltale reserves the right to take reasonable steps to verify customer identity prior to granting access or processing changes or corrections.

If you would like to change your personal information or remove it from our records, you have any of the following choices to modify or delete such information from our database: • Log in with your password and modify/delete your profile; • Send a letter to LCG Entertainment, Inc. c/o Law Office of Dan Lee Rogers P.O. Box 1233 Oakhurst, CA 93644 • E-mail us at privacy@Telltalegames.com (and if you reside in the European Economic Area you may contact our Data Protection Officer via e-mail at dpo@Telltalegames.com )

This Privacy Policy covers only information that is collected through our Sites, and does not cover information that may be collected through software downloaded from the Sites. Our Sites may contain links to other websites. Please be aware that LCG/Telltale is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other websites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our Site(s) to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information.

If you have any questions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us at: LCG Entertainment, Inc. c/o Law Office of Dan Lee Rogers P.O. Box 1233 Oakhurst, CA 93644 or e-mail us at: privacy@Telltalegames.com

For users who reside in the European Economic Area, you may contact our Data Protection Officer by e-mail at dpo@Telltalegames.com.

**Special Note to Parents and Guardians**

Anyone using the Internet should ensure that their privacy is being protected. LCG/Telltale is committed to complying fully with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act. We ask parents and guardians of children to discuss what information should be released on the Internet, especially personal information. LCG/Telltale does not condition a child’s participation in any of the activities available on our Sites on the disclosure of more information than is reasonably necessary to participate in the activity.

Within the United States, LCG/Telltale does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13 and, outside of the United States, LCG/Telltale does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the relevant age threshold applicable to the country or jurisdiction where a user may reside. When a user in the 13-18 year old age category submits personally identifiable information, LCG/Telltale may, in accordance with applicable laws or regulations or at LCG/Telltale’s discretion, request a parent or guardian’s e-mail address to notify the parent or guardian of the activity of the user in this age category.

In accordance with applicable rules and regulations, or at LCG/Telltale’s discretion, some areas of our Sites or Services may not be accessible to anyone under the age of 18, regardless of whether a parent or guardian has provided consent.

**Security**

LCG/Telltale has security measures in place to protect and prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. LCG/Telltale uses industry standard efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal identifiable information such as firewalls. While “perfect security” does not exist on the Internet, our technical experts at LCG/Telltale work hard to ensure your secure use of our services.

**Merger or Acquisition**

While LCG/Telltale does not sell, rent, or otherwise disclose personal information collected from and about its users to third parties except as specifically stated in this Privacy Policy, please note that in the event of a merger, acquisition, reorganization, bankruptcy, or other similar event, LCG/Telltale’s customer information (including your personally identifiable information) may be transferred to LCG/Telltale’s successors or assigns, if permitted by and done in accordance with applicable law.

**Your California Privacy Rights**

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits California residents to request from companies conducting business in California a list of third parties to which the company may have disclosed personally identifiable information for direct marketing purposes. LCG/Telltale does not share your personal information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes; however, if you believe LCG/Telltale may have shared such information, please feel free to contact LCG/Telltale at privacy@Telltalegames.com or contact us at the physical address noted above (and provide contact information so that we may respond to you). LCG/Telltale will promptly respond to any requests in accordance with applicable law.

**California Do Not Track Disclosure**

Some of our users may set a Do Not Track (“DNT”) privacy preference in their web browser. DNT allows users another method of informing websites and services that they do not want certain information about their website visits collected over time and across different websites. We do not respond to DNT signals from browsers, and if a DNT signal is sent to us we will continue to collect personal information as may be permitted by this Privacy Policy and applicable law.

**Privacy Shield**

LCG/Telltale complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union to the United States. LCG/Telltale has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles. If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification, please visit https://www.privacyshield.gov/ . LCG/Telltale is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the Federal Trade Commission (FTC). Please note that LCG/Telltale tries to minimize disclosures of personal data as reasonably practical because of its responsibility and potential liability in cases of onward transfers to third parties.

**Arbitration of Disputes**

Subject to any legal restrictions that may be applicable to residents located outside of the United States, any and all disputes or claims arising out of this Privacy Policy and/or your relationship with LCG/Telltale or the Site shall be submitted to binding arbitration according to the applicable rules of the American Arbitration Association (“AAA”). THIS MEANS THAT YOU ARE WAIVING YOUR RIGHT TO SUE LCG/TELLTALE IN COURT AND HAVE A JURY TRIAL. Before submitting any matter to arbitration, you and LCG/Telltale each agree to first attempt in good faith to settle any such dispute or claim. If a dispute or claim arises, either party to this Agreement will send a notice to the other. LCG/Telltale may send a notice to you at either the e-mail address it has on file for your or your physical address (if available). You may contact LCG/Telltale by sending a notice to: CEO, LCG/Telltale, Inc., PO Box 9737, San Rafael, CA 94912-9737. The 30-day period to work in good faith to settle any disputes or claims will start on the day that notice is received by the party receiving notice. If the dispute or claim is not able to be settled in good faith, then the matter be submitted to AAA arbitration and conducted under the Commercial Arbitration Rules of AAA. The parties to the arbitration shall evenly divide any and all costs of the arbitration. You specifically agree that no claim or dispute may be arbitrated (or brought in a court of law) on a class-action basis. Each party may bring an action only in an individual capacity in a single action, and not as a plaintiff or class member in any purported class or representative proceeding, and the arbitrator may not consolidate or join any arbitration actions against LCG/Telltale. If the preceding sentence is not deemed to be enforceable, then this section will be considered void and extinguished. The arbitration shall take place exclusively in Marin County, California and shall be governed by California law without regard to its conflict of law provisions. Parties may however seek interim relief, including (and without limitation) any injunctive or other equitable relief, from either the Court or AAA arbitrator to protect against infringement of any intellectual property interests or if interim relief is otherwise deemed by a party to be proper. The arbitration may be conducted in person, through submission of documents, by phone or online. The arbitrator will make a written decision regarding the arbitration and, upon request from either party, will provide a statement of reasons for the decision. The arbitrator must follow California law (and federal law if applicable), and any award may be challenged on that basis. Subject to applicable laws, either party may request a court to compel arbitration, to stay a proceeding pending arbitration, or to confirm, modify, vacate or enter judgment on the award entered by the arbitrator.  
If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request.  
Under certain conditions, more fully described on the Privacy Shield website, you may invoke binding arbitration when other dispute resolution procedures have been exhausted.

**Translations**

If this Privacy Policy is translated to a language other than English, and there is any difference between a translated version and the English-language version, the terms of the English-language version will be considered controlling in order to resolve or clarify any differences.  
(Revised August 20, 2019)
